asexyservice.com 2017-07-27

# ASexyService.com - Escorts, Body Rubs, Strippers, Models and Sugar Babies

ASexyService.com respects your privacy and wants to inform you of our Privacy Policy:

Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy

Upon every interaction with ASexyService.com and services (together, the “Website”), you signify you accept this Privacy Policy. If for any reason you do not accept the Websites Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use immediately as you are not authorized to use the Website without said acceptance.

Collection of Personal Information

The website collects personal information whenever you use paid or “premium” features, create or update an account, request information or communicate with us, and otherwise visiting or using this Website’s products and services. The collected information may include without limitation users first name, last name, email address, phone number, order history, and other non-public information. We allow you to use your credit card numbers in order to use premium features but we do not store credit card numbers on file for your protection.

This website uses your information to:

1\.     Enhance your user experience

2\.     Inform you of new promotions, features, terms

3\.     Contact you regarding problems with your posts and account information

4\.     Inform you of a response to your ad

5\.     Improve the Website

6\.     Control use of the Website including monitoring posts, replies, and user accounts.

7\.     Enforce the Terms of Use (collectively, the “Activities”).

You authorize this Website to send you email to respond to your communications and administer Activities.

Collecting Non-Personal Information

This Website will receive non-personal information from you when your use this site in order to enhance your viewing experience. This non-personal information will be gathered through the use of cookies, recording IP addresses, server logs, 3rd party tags, browser specifications and other tools recorded during analysis of this Website to provide a better user experience.

Disclosing Information

Under certain circumstances, this Website may disclose personal information to agents and operators under confidentiality; (1) to vendors such as payment processers and other service providers; (2) to provide you with our products and services; (3) to provide you customer service; (4) to respond to subpoenas and legal process; or (5) as otherwise authorized by you.

Contact from Website & Opting Out

The website will occasionally send out information with announcements regarding updates and account details. You may elect to not receive these at any time by following standard opt-out procedures. These procedures include (1) clicking the “unsubscribe” button in the footer of the email; (2) replying to the message and including the single word “unsubscribe” in the message body.

Age Restrictions

Some material on this website is for mature audiences only. By accepting this agreement, you agree that you are at least 18 years of age. This Website is not to be used by children under 18 years of age and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years of age. This website does not target children as an audience and it is the parents responsibility to monitor their child’s Internet use. This Website does not collect age information on its “viewers”. This Website does not collect age information from “posters” besides what was submitted by a user upon creating an account. You are responsible for your account and should not share passwords with anyone.

External Links

You must be aware that this Website contains links to other sites on the World Wide Web which are maintained by other organizations and are not affiliated with our Website. These links are not posted on the behalf of this Website and we do not control, endorse, or guarantee privacy standards on these sites. If you follow a link to an outside site, you release this Website from all liability resulting from going to said site.

Data & Security

This Website makes large efforts to store data in a secure way by following industry standard procedures against abusive and unauthorized access. Please be aware that any site on the World Wide Web is susceptible to online threats. In result, for the few select categories that require payment, this Website does not store any banking credentials such as credit card numbers. It may be a small inconvenience to manually input payment information every time, however this is in efforts to protect your information. If you follow a link to an external site (referenced in “External Links” Section), you release this website from any liability resulting from transactions on said external sites.

Updates

This Privacy Policy will be updated. You can see the effective date of last revision at the top of this Privacy Policy. You should check for updates frequently to stay up to date because every time you access, post, browse, or effectively “use” the site, you are accepting the most revised version described by the revision date above.

Contact

Please contact admin@asexyservice.com with any questions about this Privacy Policy.
